监狱里要有等级秩序 先生们
We need a pecking order inside, gentlemen.
这样我们才能控制外面的局势 懂吗
So we have control on the outside. Okay? Period.
咬死他
Get him!
里面没有领头人 麦克
There're no leaders inside, Mike.
为什么不选个新管事的呢
Why don't you pick new leaders?
没有人可以选
There's no new leaders to pick from.
起来 黑鬼
Get up, nigga!
我不想走
I don't wanna go.
他们会给你一个新身份
They're gonna give you a new identity.
帮你找个工作
They'll help you get a job.
凯尔怎么样
How's Kyle?
他接受了州北的工作
He took a job upstate.
你够走运 这船上没毒品
You're lucky there wasn't drugs on this boat,
你放了船上那三个人 连搜身都没做
you left three guys on deck, you didn't even frisk 'em.
每一天 你们都要选择
Everyday, you will choose
是提升自我
whether to study
还是虚度光阴
or wether to blow this off.
哦 不
Oh! No!
别抵抗了 婊子
Give it up you bitch!
我想出去走走
I wanna go for a walk.
不在你身边的话我们就没法保护你
We can't protect you if we're not with you.
所以麦洛 在不在囚犯名单上
So, Milo... Is he listed on the Inmate roster?
他做了什么 麦克 他难道直接从前门走出去了吗
What'd he do? Mike, what did he just walk out the front gate?
监狱里不太平 意味着外面也不太平
Wars inside means war on the outside.
唯一的区别是
The only difference is
监狱里的战争没有无辜的受害者
no innocent victims during the inside war.
在外面 杀害无辜的人则是战争胜利的诀窍
Outside, innocent victims is how you fight the war.
911 您有什么紧急情况
911, what's your emergency?
我被枪击了 所有人都被
I've been shot. Everybody's been...
女士 你还在吗
Ma'am, are you still there?
我听到了枪声
I heard gunfire.
你被击中了吗 女士
Have you been shot, ma'am?
如果你不能说话 随便按一下键盘上的数字
If you can't speak, simply press any number on your keypad.
很好 枪手还在活动中吗
Good, is the shooter still active?
你知道有多少受害者吗
Do you know how many victims?
在这个操蛋地方 每个人都是受害者
Everybody in this motherfucker about to be a victim.
如果你们来了
If y'all show up,
你们这群狗娘养的也要成受害者
you motherfuckers gonna be victims too.
喂
Yeah.
你在去枪击场所的路上吗
Hey, you heading towards the shots fired?
-在路上  -怎么样
- Yeah. - What is it?
不确定 你来了吗
Not sure. You on your way?
我得先去送点东西
I gotta drop something off first,
但我会去的
but, yeah, I'll be there.
NEW字幕组翻译
翻译  Chanandler
翻译  炭炭
翻译  江湖
翻译  大老牛
翻译  星树
翻译  Melody
校对  Adlon
校对  头上长仙草
时间轴  长颂
时间轴  konosjda
时间轴  斤日
啦啦队  千阳
总监  千阳
CSEG克隆字幕提取组
提取  Caliro
@CSEG克隆字幕提取组
拜托 快接电话
Come on, please answer.
-拜托  -嗨 麦克
- Come on. Hi. - Hey, Mike.
嗨 你做什么呢
What are you doing?
嗯 不关你的事
Um, none of your business.
好吧 那你要做多久呢
Well, how long are you gonna be doing that?
希望整个晚上吧
Well, the hope is all night.
你要什么
What do you need?
操 我去 没事了 抱歉
Fucking come on. All right, never mind, sorry.
操 天哪
Fuck. Jesus.
快接
Come on.
-喂 怎么了  -你干吗呢
- Yeah, what's up? - What are you doing?
什么 我他妈在睡觉
What? Well, I was fucking sleeping.
怎么了
What's up?
我得让你帮我看点东西
I gotta drop something by for you to watch.
你弄了什么东西 小狗还是啥
What you get, like, a dog or something?
不是
I did not.
好吧 那是啥 麦克
Well, what is it, Mike?
我一会就到
I'm gonna be there in a minute.
好吧
All right.
我不需要保姆
I don't need a babysitter.
对 你需要的是证人保护计划 艾丽丝
No, what you need is witness protection, Iris.
拜你所赐 计划泡汤了
We all know how that went.
我只需要一个善良的世界
I just need a kind world.
好吧 那并不存在
Well, those don't exist.
你的行为只是拖延了不可避免的事情
And all you're doing is prolonging the inevitable here, Iris.
金斯敦不是个城市
Kingstown is not a city.
它是个小镇 所有事情在这里都无所遁形
It's a town and nothing stays hidden in a town.
所以要么你离开 否则他就会找到你 就这样
So either you leave or he's gonna find you, period.
是 你的情况也一样
Yeah, same goes for you.
操 好吧 你渴吗
Shit. Okay. You thirsty?
不渴
No.
你好
Hi.
麦克
Uh, Mike.
我能跟你说句话吗
Uh, can I get a word with you, please?
去 好 坐里面吧
Go... Yeah. Sit inside.
-来吧  -好
- Come on. - Yeah.
那他妈是谁
Who the fuck is that?
是我办公室那个女孩 和那三个被杀的
It's the girl from my office with the three feds
联邦探员一起的
who were murdered.
-我操  -对
- Oh. Shit. - Yeah.
我不知道我们找到她了
I didn't know we found her.
我们没有 是我找到的
We didn't. I did.
好吧 你真行
Look, good for you,
那他妈的把她藏到你小屋里去
then go hide her at your fucking cabin.
不行 我不能留她一个人在那
I can't. I cannot leave her alone.
好吗 她被麦洛折磨得够呛
All right. She's been put through the wringer by Milo.
我让她去证人保护计划她不去
Okay, look, and I put her in WitPro and she jumped it.
我他妈不管
I don't give a shit.
我这不能留她 麦克
I can't have her here, Mike,
你懂吧 我怀孕的妻子和咱妈还在这
you know, with my pregnant wife and our mother.
你他妈疯了是吗
Are you out of your fucking mind?
我要去处理点棘手的事情
I just gotta put a lid on a fucking problem.
好吗 就几个小时
Okay. It's just for a few hours.
什么事都不会比一个妓女
Problems don't get bigger than the hooker
在咱妈的客厅里棘手 麦克
in our mother's living room, Mike.
-拜托 她是  -迈克尔
- Come on... - Michael?
操 你个傻逼
Fuck. Asshole.
嗯
Yeah.
抱歉现在太晚了
Sorry it's so late.
我们只是找个地方
We're just looking for a place to...
-等等  -让我走
- Wait, wait. - Let me go. Let me...
这他妈什么事
What the fuck?
-让我走 麦克  -别慌 放轻松
- Let me fucking go, Mike! - Woah, easy. Easy. Easy.
-你他妈是个畜生  -找一个安全的地方...
- Let me go. You're a fucking dog. - Looking for a safe place...
-让我走  -发生什么了
- Let me go! Let me go. - What is happening?
-放轻松  -来客人了
- Huh! - We have a guest.
楼上有一间空房
Um, we have a spare room upstairs.
特蕾西 你能带她去看看吗
Tracy, would you show her where it is?
-当然 来吧  -谢谢
- Sure. All right. - Thank you.
不会太久 对不住了各位
It's just for a minute. Sorry, guys.
-你好 我是特蕾西  -我是艾丽丝
- Hi, I'm Tracy. - I'm Iris.
名字真好听
That's a pretty name.
不是我真名 我瞎起的
It's not mine. I made it up.
她遇到麻烦了吗
She in trouble?
是啊 妈
Yeah. Yes, Mom.
-哪种麻烦  -最糟的那种
- What kind of trouble? - The worst kind.
但根本不是她的问题
And none of it is her fault.
好吧
Okay.
你什么时候回来接她 麦克
When you coming back for her, Mike?
今天下午 晚上吧 我会解决的
This afternoon, this evening. And I'll get this done.
好 行吧 越早越好
Okay, well, the sooner the better.
-好  -我真的不想
- Yeah. -'Cause I don't need
-引火上身  -好 我知道
her trouble to become our trouble.
是啊 她人都来了 不是吗
Yeah, it's kind of already is, isn't it.
行吧 妈的 我爱你
Well, you know, fuck, I love you,
那个啥 真该死
but, you know, God damn.
-我知道 去睡吧  -操
- I know. Go to bed. - Fuck.
犯罪现场鉴证科
金斯敦验尸官
麦克 惨无人道啊 他妈的一团糟
Mike, it's a fucking mess. It's just a fucking mess.
我们放你兄弟一马 他就这么对我们
We give your boy a pass and this is how he treats us.
不 不 不是邦尼下的命令
No, no, no. Fucking bunny didn't order this shit.
这是里面人的命令
This came from the inside. Jesus.
-天啊  -还以为他们在里面没有领头人呢
Thought there were no fucking leaders on the inside.
确实没有
There aren't.
那就完全说不通啊
That makes no fucking sense.
听着 正是因为里面没有领头人
Look, when there's no leaders inside,
个个才都想称霸王 明白吗
everyone tries to play leader, okay?
老天爷 伊恩
Jesus Christ, Ian.
山中无老虎 猴子称大王
Tail's wagging the fucking dog, right?
才造成现在这个局面
And this is the result. Jesus.
里面一团糟 麦克
It's rough in there, Mike.
我之前也见识过
I've seen it before.
你还真没见过 麦克
No, you haven't seen this, Mike.
别 别在犯罪现场吐 快出去
No, don't throw up on my crime scene, come on.
出去
Outside!
操
Fuck.
麦克 这场面你没见过吧
So, Mikey, you ever seen anything like this before?
反正我是真没见过
Because I sure as hell haven't.
没 这样的真没见过
No, not like this.
地方检察官说这算得上大规模枪击事件了 麦克
DA's calling it a mass shooting, Mike.
这就是帮派枪战 他明白 我们也都明白
Well, it's a gang shooting. He knows it. We know it.
天啊
Jesus.
是啊 如果他们只是开车扫射
Well, yeah, it was a gang shooting
把房子打成马蜂窝 那才是帮派枪战
when they drove by and hosed the fucking house down.
但是又来一队人特意进屋里
When that next group walked through,
麦克 他妈的挨个处决每个人
Mikey, fucking executing people,
这场事件 性质就变了
it became... It became something else.
这事要上国家新闻了
Welcome to national news.
-长官  -什么
- Sir. - Yeah.
找到一把凶器
We got a murder weapon.
只有我打电话报警了吗
Am I the only motherfucker that called this in?
有位受害者正跟调度员通话时被射杀了
Mikey, Dispatch was on with one of the vics when she was shot.
在他们进入房子之前
He told the patrol units to fucking seal off the streets
他告诉巡警说要他妈封锁街道
before they pushed on the goddamn house.
无所畏惧的警察局长 我们还能说什么
Fearless fucking police chief. What can we say?
我们在那边跟他们有过交战
Yeah, we engaged them over here.
-好 我们去看看  -我带你去
- All right, let's see. - I'll show you.
我们撤到这里之后 他们就从这里出来了
So we pulled up the house. They were coming out here.
我们交火 他们疯了一样开枪
We engaged and they unleashed fucking hell on us.
妈的
Fuck.
沿着这条巷子跑了
Dipped down this alleyway and took off.
但其中一个人掉了这个
But one of them dropped this.
这他妈的可不是帮派的枪
That's not a fucking gangster gun.
看看这玩意儿
Look at this thing.
麦克 这把枪新加了导轨系统
Mikey, this thing's got an added rail system.
可提高武器射击稳定性 减轻武器重量
还有...还他妈装了枪口制退器
It's got... It's got a fucking muzzle brake on it.
真行 这他妈都是枪械师了吧
Great, now they're fucking gunsmiths now.
不 他们才不知道怎么做这些东西
No, they don't know how to do that shit
除非是从墨西哥帮那里搞来的
unless they got it from the Mexicans.
这条巷子查了吗
You case this alley yet?
没有 长官 他们说要等特警队来
No, sir, they told us to wait for SWAT.
-有手电筒吗  -有
- You got a torch? - Yeah.
看到了
Yeah.
跟着这个
Follow this right here.
操 麦克 要不还是等等特警队的人
Fuck, Mikey, maybe we should wait for SWAT.
如果等这家伙血流干死透了
Well, if we wait for this guy to bleed out,
我们就真的错过很多信息了
we're not gonna know more than we already know.
而且我们他妈的什么都不知道
And we don't know fucking shit.
天啊 他就在这里
Jesus, he's right there.
我叫麦克·麦克拉斯基
My name's Mike McLusky.
你知道我是谁吗
You know who I am?
你听过我的名字吗
You know my name?
我知道你
I know who you are.
我可以过去跟你聊聊吗
Can I come over and talk to you
你不会冲我开枪吧
and you not fucking shoot me?
我开枪不了 伙计
I can't shoot you, man.
我没枪了
Dropped my gun.
好 我这就过去
All right, I'm coming over.
他们开枪 我们也开枪
They start shooting and we start shooting.
我们跑 然后我的肚子就他妈裂开了
We run, and my fucking stomach just opened up
五脏六腑都要掉出来了
and everything trying to fall out.
是啊 子弹从沥青上弹起来
Yeah, a ricochet off the asphalt.
就这么划开了你的肚子
Sliced you as it goes by.
我要完蛋了
I'm fucked then.
没错 你确实要完蛋了
Yeah, you're fucked anyway.
隔壁差不多死了20多个人
There's two dozen dead people next door.
明白吗
All right.
都要完蛋 老兄
Everything's gone so south, man.
我没想到那群混蛋会在公交站
I didn't count on motherfuckers doing drive-bys
飞车扫射
on bus stops.
完全他妈的无差别扫射
Fucking shooting people's grandmas and shit.
他们打算这么玩
That's how they wanna play,
那我们就跟他们玩到底
then we gonna motherfucking play.
我们下次就袭击教堂
They gonna hit motherfucking churches next.
是吗 那他们接下来会干什么
Is that right? Then what they gonna do?
我来告诉你 他们会做什么吧
I'm gonna tell you what they're gonna fucking do.
他们会袭击学校
They'll hit the schools
然后会找去你妈工作的地方
and then they'll find out where your fucking mother works.
冤冤相报 直到尽头 知道吗
This only goes one way until it stops, okay?
没有人是赢家
It's a lose fucking lose for everybody.
没法停手了 伙计
Ain't no way to make it stop, man.
现在群龙无首
Head been cut off all the chickens
他们会到处乱跑 制造流血事件
and they just running around, bleeding everywhere.
所以你们就跟墨西哥人合作了是吗
So you all paired up with Mexicans, did ya?
血帮跟雅利安人合作了
Bloods tied up with the Aryans.
-我不会告诉你的  -你这样好吗
- I ain't telling you shit. - Oh, is that right?
从我过来开始你就一直在跟我瞎扯
You've been saying shit to me since I walked over.
为什么就不能跟我说点
Why don't you say some shit to me
有意义的东西呢
that fucking makes a difference?
天哪 你能不能先过去啊史蒂夫
Will you get the fuck out of here, for God sakes, Stevie.
说吧 行不行
Come on, how about it?
说点有意义的东西
Say something that makes a fucking difference.
那群畜生在公交站把我妹妹杀死了
They fucking killed my sister at that bus stop.
她才八岁 当时周围就没帮派成员
Eight years old. Not a gangbanger in sight.
我懂了
I understand.
那你觉得你们刚在房子里的所作所为能阻止这种事发生吗
And you think what you just did in there is gonna stop it?
在你们选出新的头目之前
Until the chickens get their fucking heads,
所有公交站 所有商场 任何地方
every fucking bus stop, every mall, everywhere,
都会发生这种事 你懂吗
just like this. You understand?
到时候没人敢出门
No one can leave their house.
我快死了 伙计
I'm dying, man.
对 是啊
Yes, you are.
你说的对
You ain't wrong.
你说的那两个确实合作了 你说的对
Who you said is with who, you ain't wrong.
是谁下的命令
Who ordered this?
看着我 是谁下的命令
Look at me. Who ordered this?
没人组织 伙计 这就是问题所在
Nobody, man. That's the fucking problem.
没人下命令
Ain't nobody ordering nothing.
那帮混蛋就是想出门打仗
Motherfuckers just out here warring and shit.
就是想打仗 伙计
Just... Just warring, man.
我要去跟邦尼聊聊
I'm gonna go talk to Bunny.
麦克 你得让他想办法停下来
Mike, you gotta get him to find the fucking off switch.
镇上要封锁了
This town's gonna get locked down.
要是谁有办法能封锁这里 伊恩
If somebody was gonna shut it down, Ian,
他们肯定早就停手了
they would've done it already.
这个地方可封锁不住
This place don't lock down.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
怎么了
What's goin' on?
这工作真是太操蛋了 麦克
This fucking job, Mike.
我对天发誓
I swear to God...
我知道
I know.
人们总问我为什么不找男朋友
And people wonder why I don't have a boyfriend.
不 我知道为什么
No, I get why.
你保持单身是因为你比其他人都聪明
I mean, you're single because you're smarter than everybody.
你想让大家都知道这点
And you let everybody know it.
你看 你被冒犯时会笑
You see? And you laugh when you get insulted.
你感到冒犯是因为你笑了
And you feel insulted 'cause you laugh.
就是这么复杂 你这个人真让人头疼
Fucking complicated. You're a fucking pain in the ass.
好了 振作点好吗
Hey, come on. Cheer up, okay?
看着我
Look at me.
这工作如果容易 那谁都能干了 对吧
If it was easy, everyone would do it, okay?
你可是老大
You're a boss.
好了
Come on.
你可也是单身啊 麦克
You know you're single too, Mike?
是啊 但我单身的原因跟你可不一样
Yeah, for very different fucking reasons.
金斯敦市 警察
马里奥手机维修 立等可取
邦尼
Bunny.
收售交易 移动电话维修
你知道我是谁 有事留言
Yo, you know who it is. Leave a message.
邦尼
Bunny!
邦尼 你个混蛋
Bunny! You motherfucker!
怎么回事
What the fuck?
他在这吗
Hey. He here?
好 准备好
Yeah, just be ready.
麦克 局面失控了
Mike, this shit getting out of hand.
是啊 你以为呢
Yeah, you think?
刚在23号大街 你知道我进去了个什么地方
What the fuck did I just walk into on 23rd Street?
你们他妈的都干了些什么
What the fuck did you do?
你手下以你的名义制造了一场大屠杀
It was a fucking massacre under your flag!
-不 不是以我的名义 不是  -是吗
- No, not my flag. No. - Yeah?
不是我指使的 不是 我没有
I did not call that. No. I can't.
我没让他们这么做 是监狱里面的人指使的
I can't call that. That shit came from inside.
我跟一个枪手聊过了 好吗
I talked to the shooter, all right?
指令不是从监狱放出来的
It did not come from the fucking inside,
如果不是你指使的
so unless it came from you,
那就是有人在暗地谋划什么
somebody's fucking cooking something up.
-肯定是那些狱警  -行了吧
- It's the fucking guards! - Oh, come on.
那些混蛋不管我们
Them motherfuckers giving us their backs.
他们把一个蠢货从背后捅死
They shank a fool in the back,
留他的尸体在床上腐烂
leave the body in the cot to rot.
他们把尸体跟垃圾一起扔掉了 麦克
They throwing motherfuckers out with the fucking trash, Mike.
听我说 有两件事
Listen to me. Two things.
你让外面的手下都停手
You gotta sit everyone down on the outside.
好了 然后你们都得承认
Okay, then you all have to agree
你们这些船就是没有船长
that none of your ships have fucking captains,
在选出船长之前 所有船都不许出港
and until they do, no ships leave the fucking port.
这比喻你听懂了吗
You understand the metaphor?
那些狱警呢 兄弟
What about the fucking guards, man?
我会解决狱警的问题
I'll handle the fucking guards.
我们需要的就是监狱里的秩序 老哥
Yeah, we need some order on the inside, cuz.
那些混账狱警也得停手
Them motherfucking guards need to sit their ass down too.
找新管事的需要时间
It takes time to find a leader.
-而现在...  -是啊
- And right now... - Yeah.
刚准备选某个人当管事的
A leader tries to rise,
结果他到晚上就死了
and that motherfucker is dead by nightfall.
好吧 听着 我会让那些狱警
Okay, look, I'll get the fucking guards
有所作为
to take their blinders off.
你必须现在就休战
You gotta manage this truce like fucking now
因为国民警卫队要开始
'cause the National Guard is gonna start
在这些街上巡逻了
patrolling these streets.
我们都知道他们是怎么处理这种破事儿的
And we've seen how they handle shit.
你...你得去调停这破事儿
You... You gonna need to referee this shit.
去他妈的 我调停个屁
Fuck I do. I ain't refereeing shit.
你失心疯了吗
You out of your mind?
那我们他妈的怎么让我们那四个狗娘养的
How the fuck we gonna have four motherfucking enemies
死对头好好坐下
sit their ass down
然后在没有瑞典人参与的情况下互相残杀呢
and not kill each other without a Sweden?
瑞士是永久中立国
啥 瑞士人
What, a Switzerland?
我他妈不是瑞士人 去他妈的
I'm not fucking Switzerland. Fuck that.
老兄 去他的 老兄
Man, kiss my ass, man.
不管是瑞典瑞士还是瑞什么
Sweden, Switzerland, crackerland,
你们这些狗娘养的把事态搞炸的时候
whatever cracker-ass country
随意一个狗屁国家也都会
babysitting the other cracker-ass country
去收拾另一个狗屁国家的烂摊子
when y'all motherfuckers be blowing shit up.
就是那样
That.
麦克 我们需要一个调停人
We need a mediator, Mike.
不然的话 这些破事只会
Otherwise, all this shit is gonna do
让这场战争一直恶化下去
is make this war worse.
-操  -你看到这烂摊子了
- Fuck. - You saw that shit.
行
Okay.
行吧行吧
Okay, okay.
我有主意了
I have an idea.
我就在这儿 兄弟 跟我说吧
I'm right here, man. Hit me with it.
好吧 不过这一次你必须要
All right, you're gonna have to
确确实实地相信我 邦尼
really fucking trust me on this one, though, Bunny,
我说 确确实实地他妈的相信我 好吗
and I mean really fucking trust me, okay?
会有些痛 但会成功的
It's gonna sting, but it will work.
我保证我会遵守对你的承诺
And I promise I will keep my word to you.
-会多疼  -很操蛋的疼
- How bad it's gonna sting? - Oh, like a motherfucker.
一切结束了之后
And when it's over,
你就再也不用躲在这破屋顶上了
you won't have to hide out in this fucking rooftop anymore.
行吗
Okay?
我这一生都在这破地方
I spent my whole life in this sorry-ass motherfucker.
不知道为什么 每一次事情都会更糟
Every time, somehow, this bitch get worse.
就在你觉得不可能再糟了的时候
And just when you think it can't get any worse than it is,
兄弟 事情总会出其不意
man, this motherfucker find a way.
是啊
Yeah.
我这次相信你
I'ma trust you on this.
好 好吧
Yeah. All right.
很好
Good.
那就三小时后见
Now I'll see you in three hours.
好好好 去吧
All right, all right, all right, do it.
-三小时后 好吗  -好 好
- Three hours, okay? - Yeah, yeah.
别迟到 也别带一大帮人来
Don't be late. Don't bring a fucking army.
保持现状 让大家都呆在这儿
And just keep people here for the status quo.
三小时 好吗
Three hours, okay?
在
Yeah.
嘿 是我 醒了吗 我有个想法
Hey, it's me. You awake? I have an idea.
用于治疗焦虑症 失眠等
我吃了两片阿普唑仑 喝了三杯威士忌
Two Xanax, three whiskeys.
你有什么想法
What's your idea?
要是我能把四个帮派的头目都给你弄来呢
What if I could get you the leaders to all four gangs?
所有人都在交战 要是我能把他们都给你带来呢
Everyone that's at war. What if I can give them all to you?
那我要帮你做什么
What's it gonna cost me?
我需要你把他们关到监狱里 不能在城里
Well, I need them in the pen, not county.
他们在假释中吗
They on parole?
有两个是
Two of them are.
一个不是 另一个我不知道
One isn't. The other one, I don't know.
因为什么指控
What's the charge?
被发现持有枪支
Found in possession of firearm.
-那得判十年 麦克  -是啊
- That's 10 years, Mike. - Yes, it is.
但是问题在这儿 伊芙琳
But here's the catch, Evelyn.
我需要你撤销所有指控
I'm gonna need you to drop all the charges.
那为什么要指控他们呢 麦克
Why charge them at all, Mike?
因为我需要他们在里面
Because I need them on the inside
选出新的领导人 这就是原因
to pick new leaders, that's why.
你想让我把这四个最恶名昭著的
You want me to arrest the leaders
监狱帮派的领导人抓起来
of the four worst prison gangs
为的就是让他们在监狱里
so they can reinstate a leadership structure
重建领导体系吗
inside the prison?
没错
Exactly.
你知道这听起来多他妈离谱吗 麦克
You have any idea how fucking insane that sounds, Mike?
伊芙琳 你比任何人都要清楚
Evelyn, you, more than anybody, knows
里面的人才是指挥外面的人
that the inside runs the outside, okay.
但是现在里面没人统领
Nobody right now is running the inside.
听着 除非你还想继续看到
Look, unless you want to keep meeting
在公交车站等男朋友的
over the body of a 16-year-old girl
十六岁女孩的尸体
waiting for her boyfriend at a bus stop.
我只是不明白
I just don't see it.
但我明白 好吗 我明白
Well, I do, okay? I see it.
所以你要相信我
So you gotta trust me.
好
Okay.
很好 听着 很快就要开始了
All right, look, this is gonna happen soon,
所以准备好 我会打给你
so be ready. I'll call you.
嘿 恭喜啊
Hey. Congratulations.
搞什么 麦克
What the fuck, Mike!
怎么了
The fuck, what?
我不需要你鬼鬼祟祟地接近我
I don't need you sneaking up on me.
什么
What?
我只是走到你车道的中间
I just walked up the middle of your fucking driveway.
看到门大开着 冷静点
The door's wide open. Chill out.
你他妈来这干啥
The fuck you doing here?
我听说他们把监狱交给你了
I heard they gave you the prison.
监狱长没了监狱
Well, when wardens lose the prison,
就等于丢了工作 这只是暂时的
they lose their jobs, it's temporary.
我要给你看点东西
Something I need to show you.
什么东西
Show me what?
这东西对你新职位有直接影响
It has an immediate impact on your new position.
行 你葫芦里卖的什么药
Okay, what's the play?
帐篷城需要新领导
We need new leaders in Tent City
而我们需要挑选新领导
and we need to pick them.
帐篷城只有我说了算
Only order in Tent City is mine.
为什么要搞这出
Why fuck with that?
因为我们需要里面恢复秩序
'Cause we need order on the inside
来让外面也恢复秩序 这就是原因
to get order on the outside. That's why.
就让他们自相残杀吧
Fucking let them kill each other.
这破事已经发展到街头了
This shit has already spilled out on the street
事态非常失控 好吗
in a real fucking way, okay,
他们早晚会去扫荡
and it's only a matter of time
你孩子的学校 体育场和教堂
before they start hosing down your kids' fucking schools,
只是时间问题 好吗
the playgrounds, the churches, right?
我们都不希望这样
We don't want that.
我需要带武器吗
Do I need a weapon?
操 我带了一把
Fuck, I have one.
让我换身衣服 拿把手枪
Let me change and get my pistol.
那个 对了 你副手是谁
Oh, hey, who do you got as your second, by the way?
卡尼
Carney.
操 真的吗
Fuck, really?
你确定他那态度能做得了这工作吗
Are you sure he's got the right attitude for the job?
确定 只有他那种态度才能在这种工作里幸存
Yeah, he's got the only attitude that survives this job.
不 你也幸存了 卡里姆
No, you fucking survived, Kareem.
我只是没死 但谈不上幸存
I lived. I wouldn't say I survived.
-车上见  -好
- I'll meet you in the car. - All right.
你有找人聊聊吗
You talking to anybody?
聊什么
About what?
我他妈的能跟谁聊
Who the fuck am I gonna talk to?
你都跟谁聊你经历的这些破事
Who do you talk to for all the shit you been through?
我不跟任何人聊 兄弟
Ah, I don't talk to anybody, man.
就...我没什么可失去的了
It's, uh... I got nothing to lose.
你弟弟都跟谁聊
Who does your brother talk to?
我不知道 大概跟他老婆吧
I don't know. Probably his wife.
他不是吧
The fuck he does.
哼 他能不是吗
Yeah, the fuck he does, right.
嗨
Hi.
你该穿便衣 罗伯特
You should blend in, Robert.
是 这就是我最像便衣的了 兄弟
Yeah, it's about as plain clothes as I get, brother.
-行吧  -史蒂夫就在仓库的屋顶
- Yeah. - Stevie's on the roof.
我的人也在仓库那儿 我和他们连着线
My boys are in that warehouse. I'm wired into them.
嘿 你觉得他们有没有
Hey, do you think they have spies looking out for PD
看着路边警察的眼线
set on the street?
那些眼线已经被我们收拾了 你懂我的 麦克
We already made their spies. You know me, Mike.
早起的鸟儿有虫吃
Early bird gets the fucking worm.
一切就绪 伙计
Everything's in place, man.
你要让我负责哪一部分
What are you dragging me into?
你负责给他们许诺并信守诺言
You're about to give your word and you will keep it.
这狗东西
This fucking guy.
你他妈在干什么
What the fuck are you doing?
我可不打算和这群混蛋讲什么公平斗争
I ain't trying to fight fair with these pieces of shit.
我们根本不是来干架的 行吗
Well, we're not fighting at all. How about that?
好吗 把枪放下
Okay? Keep it down.
都他妈的不许动
Do not fucking move!
手放车顶上
Put your hands on the roof.
枪放下 兄弟
Down, man.
开凯雷德那个 关车门
Escalade, close the fucking door.
手放车上
Hands on the car.
开奔驰的 打开后备箱
Mercedes, pop the trunk.
绕到我这一侧
Walk around the vehicle to my side.
手放引擎盖上
Put your hands on the hood.
动作快点 狗娘养的 照我说的做
Chop, chop, motherfucker, let's go.
别动
Stay.
出来
Out.
我可是王 宝贝 王不需要佩剑
I'm a king, baby. King don't need no sword.
你要真是王
If you were the king,
就不需要来这碰面了
there would be no need for this fucking meeting.
你 就你一个 去那边
You and only you walk over there.
你们这群智障 回车上去
You, fuckheads, back in the vehicle.
把车停到停车场对面 面向我
Park across the lot, facing me.
不许开回来 除非看到我招呼
Do not drive back until I wave you over.
-邦尼  -我来看看都有谁
- Bunny. - What do we got here?
用来形容"红脖子" 对素质低下思想落后的白人的蔑称
哇哦 一只愤怒的小啄木鸟
Woah, angry little peckerwood.
《汤姆叔叔的小屋》中的人物 现用以讽刺过于讨好白人的黑人
和他的"汤姆叔叔"
And Uncle Tom.
见到你真好 兄弟 感谢过来
Good to see you, man. Thanks for coming.
你好 兄弟 怎么样
My man, what's good, baby?
感觉怎么样 能走直线了吗
How you feeling? You walking straight yet?
要不要我把你丢到海里
How about I toss you in the fucking bay
看看你那肥屁股能不能游起来
and see if your fat ass can swim?
操 尽管试试 我就在你面前呢 宝贝儿
Shit, you could try. I'm right here, baby.
-来吧  -继续说 混账东西
- Let's go. - Keep talking, thug life.
瞅瞅你那肥屁股能在我枪筒下飞多高
Let's see how far up your ass I can get the barrel of my gun.
行了 伙计们
Hey. Come on, guys.
-老是这样还想和谈吗  -停车
- Is this how we keep the fucking peace? - Stop!
能把那玩意儿拿走吗
Fucking put that away, would you, please,
请你把它放回卡车里
- like in the fucking truck.
-别伤着自己了  -你 出来 出来 就你一个
-You. Out, out. Only you. - Don't hurt yourself.
你个智障东西 把车停到对面去 车头面向我
You nosepickers, park across the lot, facing me.
不许开过来 除非看到我招呼
Do not drive back until I wave you over.
很好
That's good.
麦克
Mike.
-我没见过你  -我从大急流城过来的
- I don't know you. - I'm in from Grand Rapids.
我们在金斯敦
We don't have anyone in Kingstown
没有能代表出面解决这种事的人
ready to represent us in something like this.
我怎么确保你们在金斯敦的人
How do I know your people in Kingstown
-会听从你的指令 -停车
- gonna do what you say? - Stop.
如果不听从我的指令 就别想再跟着我混
When they don't do what I say, they stop being my people.
手放方向盘上 让我看到
Hands on the wheel where I can see them.
好 各帮派到齐了
All right. Gang's all here.
墨西哥人和血帮人手拉手过来了
Mexicans and the Bloods, hand-in-hand.
你好啊 兄弟
How you living, brother?
哦 今天我们是兄弟哈
- Oh, we're brothers today? - Yeah.
是啊 试试看呗
We gonna try, huh.
老兄 你怎么把这个疯子叫来了
Man, why you bring that crazy-ass motherfucker here?
叫他来就是确保今天这片苦药能顺利咽下去
He's here to ensure that the bitter pill goes down smoothly.
各位 今天在这达成的任何停火协议
All right, any truce, any agreement,
契约或其他什么约定
anything that we come up with out here,
都必须确保在里面执行 行吧
has to be enforced inside, okay?
否则我们搞的这一出就屁用没有
Otherwise, it doesn't mean fucking dick-all.
好吗 那我们就一致同意了
Right? So we can agree upon this.
临时监狱长会再次巡视监狱 好吗
The interim warden will patrol the prison again, okay?
他会对发生的每一场冲突进行干预
And they will intervene with any and all conflicts.
伙食问题呢
What about food?
你知道那些人在里面都吃的什么吗
You know what they feed the motherfuckers in there?
所有犯人劳动项目都暂停了
All inmate work programs have been suspended.
目前所有食物都是外包的
All food is outsourced.
我们也没有厨房或冷库
We don't have a kitchen or refrigeration,
所以在我们能把犯人关回去之前
so until we can move inmates inside,
方便食品是我们能提供的最好的伙食了
bagged meals is the best we can do.
这就是暴乱的代价
That's the price of riot.
源自欧洲中世纪天主教打着"消灭女巫"旗号对异端的迫害现 引申为政治迫害
那些"猎巫行动"呢
So what about the witch hunts, huh?
你们狱警报完仇了吗
Y'all guards got all the payback yet
还是你们还想继续迫害我们
or y'all still got a little rape left in you?
对 我还有点想呢 混蛋
No, I got some left in me, motherfucker.
我他妈刚才怎么说的来着
Hey, hey, what the fuck did I say?
我他妈怎么说的
What the fuck did I say?
这他妈是要干嘛
What the fuck is this?
这位是助理地区检察官
This is the assistant district attorney.
我知道 这事跟她有啥关系
I know. What does she have to do with this?
她就是来给你们灌下苦药的
She's going to be giving you the pill you're going to swallow.
这是为了让大家保持冷静
This is to keep everybody calm.
任何突然的举动都会被视为威胁
Any sudden move will be considered a threat.
咱们也不是第一天认识了
And we've all met before
你们都清楚我是怎么对待威胁的
so you know how I deal with a threat.
你们现在因为重罪被逮捕
You're being placed under arrest
罪名是持有枪械
for felonies of possession of firearms.
等到这个山谷恢复和平
And when there's peace in the motherfucking valley,
就会撤销对你们的指控
charges against you will be dropped.
对你来说就是山谷里的每个人都和平共处
For you, that means peace in the valley for everyone.
明白吗
Okay?
他们要关押我们多久
So how long they gonna hold us?
你们在里面把你们的帮派调教好要多久
How long will it take you to get your house together inside?
不会太久
Not long.
我也不用很久
Wouldn't take me long either.
这招太狠了 麦克
Ice cold, Mike.
你想个好招 邦尼 你说一个
Name another way, Bunny. Name another way.
趴在地上
Lay on your stomach with your arms out stretched
伸开双臂 竖起大拇指
to the side and your thumbs up.
不 你给我站住 麦克
No, no, no, you stay where the fuck you are, Mike.
混蛋 你给我站这看着
Motherfucker, you stay and watch.
配合下我 邦尼 快点
Just get it done, Bunny. Come on.
来吧 伙计们 快点
Come on, boys. Come on.
去你妈的
Fuck you!
嗨 老妈
Hi, Mom.
麦克
Michael.
嗨
Hey.
操
Fuck.
天哪 老妈 怎么回事
Jesus, Mom. What the fuck?
-她不见了  -不见了
- She's gone. - Gone?
她不在房间里 她逃了
She's not in her fucking room. She's gone.
他妈的
God damn it.
他在72迈的路段只开40迈
It's going 25 in a 45.
是啊 上坡路 切诺基后面还拖着船
Yeah, uphill, towing a boat with a fucking Jeep Cherokee.
超过他就好
Just pass him.
拜托 至于吗
Come on. Really?
至于
Yeah.
是吗
Yeah?
前方司机 靠路边停车
Driver, pull to the shoulder and stop your vehicle.
没错 说你呢 靠边停车
Yeah. Yeah, you, pull over and stop your vehicle.
操
Fuck.
混蛋
Fucking asshole.
你叫我什么
What did you call me?
你个混蛋
A fucking asshole.
这人拖着个船走上坡路
The guy's pulling a boat, uphill,
你紧随他 还鸣警笛
you tailgate him, hit him with the sirens,
他不得已开过了限速
he pushes that shit to the speed limit,
然后你就把他扣下 你个混蛋
and then you pull him over? You're a fucking asshole.
闪警灯不是为了让他加速 爱因斯坦
Lights don't mean speed up, Einstein.
是让他靠边停车 别挡我路
They mean pull over and get the fuck out of my way.
行吧 但你如果非要这样
Fine, but if we're going to do this,
至少让我走个流程
let me do it right.
这又不是监狱暴动 好吗
Okay, this is not a goddamn prison riot, okay?
这只是查酒驾 别紧张
This is just a DUI. Settle down.
-我得先查他车牌  -该死
- I need to run his plate. - God damn it.
我等不及要看这傻子在湖上喝了多少酒
Can't wait to see how much this nitwit drank on the lake today.
莫拉斯 等我先就位 等等
Morass, wait till I get into position. Wait.
先生 你知道我为什么让你靠边停车吗
Sir, do you know why I pulled you over?
操 操 操 操
Fuck, fuck, fuck. Fuck, fuck, fuck.
操 莫拉斯
Fuck. Morass!
该死的
Shit.
妈的 莫拉斯
Morass!
调度中心 我是2...操
Dispatch, it's two... Fuck!
调度中心 我是A217
Dispatch, Alpha 217.
我这有一名警官受伤 多处枪伤
I got an officer down. Multiple GSW.
袭击者已被制服 另一位...
The assailant is down and the other one...
请尽快派救护车到我这
I need EMS to my location.
收到 A217 你在什么位置
Copy, Alpha 217. What's your location?
我在31号公路
It's Highway 31,
北面...操 在什么的北面...
north of, uh... Fuck. North of...
请给我一个英里标记 A217
I need a mile marker, Alpha 217.
我不知道
I don't know!
请使用你的信标 A217
Use your beacon, Alpha 217.
操
Fuck!
严禁通行
我无处可去
I have nowhere to go.
我没有家
I have no home.
求求你
Please?
我无家可归
I have no home.
这就是你家
You're home now.
囚犯押运
下车吧
Hop along.
滚开 给他让路
Yo, fuck off. Move out his way, yo.
我猜你们没向上帝祷告
Guess y'all must not pray to God up in here.
但凡你们祷告过
'Cause if you motherfuckers did,
现在也不用面对魔鬼
y'all wouldn't be staring at the devil.
《金斯敦市长》下集预告
Next time on Mayor of Kingstown...
她就这么跑了
She just ran away?
对
Yeah.
这是你的新家
This is your new home.
你认识艾丽丝吗 她就是个麻烦
You know Iris? She's trouble.
告诉你老大 我知道他已越狱 我会找到他的
Tell your boss that I know he's out, I'm gonna find him.
趴在地上 赶紧的
Down on the ground, now!
你知道我孙子是谁吗
You know who my grandson is?
我知道 女士 我们就是为他而来
I do, ma'am. Yes, that's why we're here.
不该发生这事的
It wasn't supposed to happen.
你连自己人都管不好
You can't even control your own people.
他们老大正在里面为我们办事 不许攻击他们
You don't attack them while the leaders are inside
working for us.
这账迟早要还的
There's gonna be payback.
欢迎关注新浪微博、微信公众号：CSEG克隆字幕提取组